https://chla-absc.ca/terms_of_use.php

+
Home
About CHLA-ABSCAbout CHLA-ABSCCHLA/ABSC Strategic Plan, 2018-2021By-Laws & Code of EthicsBoard of DirectorsGovernance ManualPast OfficialsMembershipCommunitiesCommunitiesCANMEDLIB ListInterlibrary Loan ListConferencesConferencesConference 2021: The Meeting PlacePublicationsContinuing EducationAdvocacy and CampaignsAwards and Funding
×
Member Log In
English
|
Français
LOGIN
CONTACT
DONATE
ADVERTISE
STORE
linkedin-icon
instagram-icon
+
Home
About CHLA-ABSCAbout CHLA-ABSCCHLA/ABSC Strategic Plan, 2018-2021By-Laws & Code of EthicsBoard of DirectorsGovernance ManualPast OfficialsMembershipCommunitiesCommunitiesCANMEDLIB ListInterlibrary Loan ListConferencesConferencesConference 2021: The Meeting PlacePublicationsContinuing EducationAdvocacy and CampaignsAwards and Funding
Terms of UseCanadian Health Libraries Association/Association des bibliothèques de la santé du Canada (CHLA/ABSC) is committed to protecting the privacy of its members.
The CHLA/ABSC website is operated in accordance with this same set of values. All personal information collected by CHLA/ABSC via this website or otherwise is done in accordance with the following privacy policy. Your registration via CHLA/ABSC's online registration service indicates your acknowledgment and acceptance of CHLA/ABSC's Terms of Use.
Personal Information
Certain processes available on this website are used to collect personal information such as “Join Us” and "Course or Conference Registration", etc. Any personally identifiable data about customers or website visitors is stored securely and used only for the purpose for which it is provided to us.
Other CHLA/ABSC members can access contact information about you, information formerly available in the printed CHLA/ABSC membership directory. Vendor representatives who hold CHLA/ABSC membership are NOT authorized to use your contact information for marketing purposes. Members are not authorized to use the membership directory information to "spam" other members.
Aggregate Data
When we collect information from you, we try to let you know at the time of collection how we will use the information. Usually, the information we collect is used in aggregate, or internally to respond to inquiries, process orders, collect confidential survey data, or to allow you to access specific member information.
The information you provide to CHLA/ABSC such as your name, address, etc. allows CHLA/ABSC to inform you about events and activities and to notify you of issues, events or special offers which may be of interest to you. By becoming a member or by requesting information or registering for events or courses offered by CHLA/ABSC, you are giving CHLA/ABSC permission to contact you by way of the information you provide.
Copyright © 2020
Canada Health Libraries Association
Contact
|
Privacy Policy
|
Terms of Use
Website powered by MemberLeap, a product of Vieth Consulting.
